GIOVANNI DE ZAYAS ANGEL

· +5358240536 · · giodezayas@gmail.com ·

Hello! I am Giovanni, I am a 24-year-old software developer with experience in development and digital transformation projects for both small companies and international groups and IoT development companies. My background includes active participation in all phases of the software development life cycle, from conception and design to implementation and post-implementation support. I am constantly seeking opportunities to learn and grow professionally, staying up to date on the latest technology trends, and looking for innovative ways to address software development challenges.

EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2024

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

SMABIT GMBH

- Development of new functionalities in Java for the Qbox1 and Qbox2 product of the COQON company to allow backup, restoration and migration of smart home systems by sending them to be stored on the server
- Development of functionalities in .NET to receive device backup files through Signal R and store them in the cloud.
- Implementation in .NET of functionalities to generate and manage Licenses for COQON company products.
- Optimization of management in Java of loading and sending information belonging to the PostgreSQL database of the Qbox2 product.
- Modification of Gateway for Zigbee devices in C language to use SQLITE database as an alternative to .csv files.
- Development of visual module for Backup and Licenses using Flutter for the COQON App.

2021 - 2022

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

AICA PHARMACEUTICAL LABORATORIES COMPANY

- Migration from Angular to React of a microfrontend module dedicated to the management of observations captured for the IT Consulting group.
- Implementation of asynchronous communication using RabbitMQ in the integration of a microservice OEaaS module developed with Nest JS dedicated to the management of multimedia files.
- Integration of OEaaS module with MinIO as a solution for storage server for multimedia files in the cloud
- Web client development with React to manage the process of capturing in-person video observations in a development process for IT consultants.
- Modeling and implementation of an App with React Native dedicated to managing and storing the capture of video observations for the team of IT consultants wirelessly, managing states and messages with the Socket.IO library

2020-2021

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY OF HAVANA "JOSE ANTONIO ECHEVERRIA"

- Frontend module development of a Web System for academic management with the JavaServer Faces framework, thus improving the user interface that already existed.
- Development of a REST API with Spring to manage evaluation, attendance and other aspects control operations within the Web System deployed at the university.
- Participation in the work team dedicated to the modeling and conception of the SQL Database that was used to store the data of the Web System

EDUCATION

2018-2021

SOFTWARE ENGINEER ,TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY OF HAVANA "JOSE ANTONIO ECHEVERRIA"

2014-2018

BACHELOR IN SCIENCE, INSTITUTE OF SCIENCES "VLADIMIR ILICH LENIN"

SKILLS

- HTML and CSS
- Java
- JavaScript
- C
- SQL Database
- WordPress

- React JS
- Flutter
- React Native
- Spring Boot
- .NET Framework
- Node JS

LENGUAGES

English

Spanish